hi and welcome to my channel I'm Andrea
dudic realtor and Associate broker with
Vista Real Estate here in Central Texas
today we're touring this spectacular
luxury home this is a $1.1 million
modern ranch style home and it's so
beautiful stay with me till the end the
outside is just as wonderful as the
inside let's take a look so this home is
truly luxurious and oneof a kind there
is roughly 3,300 square ft of living
space for bed three and 1/2 bath uh
there are two living spaces and two
dining rooms everything was redone on
this home it was technically built in
1970 but the seller redid it all from
the studs up so in the living room um
you can see we have a wood burning
fireplace that has been Tastefully
painted black woodlike tile throughout
and all the main living spaces and
carpet in the bedrooms
the kitchen is a dream it has space for
seating in the island you've got
stainless steel Thor appliances a chef's
dream we have a pop filler we have the
venting outside of the home what's
really neat is that you have your eat in
kitchen here maybe for morning coffee
light breakfast with the family maybe
nothing too big but it faces the outside
of the home so you get a nice view of
that this is one of the four bedrooms
and it's currently being used as an
office but it does have a
closet so you have three units on
property um the seller was very
meticulous about making sure that the
home was adequately insulated and that
energy bills would be great and
everything would be really efficient
brand new carpet accent wall patio
entrance from the master beams in your
ceiling and if we head on into the
master bath this is so pretty Standalone
tub um your soaking tub some beautiful
tile
and over
here you have a nice walk-in shower but
my favorite part is actually this closet
so come take a
look built and safe tons of space for
all of your clothes but something that I
thought was really neat and creative
this is actually space for a washer and
dryer in the master closet so that you
you can do laundry in here and just put
it where it needs to go so it would be
stackable you could push this back you
have a little folding station like I
said you have your safe so I think this
is a really neat space let's keep going
so what I think is really neat is he
built this with the intention of being
here this wasn't just your standard flip
he put a lot of detail into the home
this is one of the four bedrooms again
accent wall Fresh
carpet this is a very generous sized
secondary bedroom it is a full bathroom
this room is so huge you could really do
anything you wanted to it but I wanted
to highlight that you could do a a
dining space here you could have a bar
area you can see there's actually a wet
bar uh another wine fridge sink all of
that it's really pretty but you have no
shortage of entertaining space and this
is technically the laundry
room since you have that other one in
the master but what's really neat is
that but while everything was basically
redone some of the original brick was
left and I think it just adds a nice
little touch to the property kind of
leaving some of the natural elements so
through the
garage from the front this actually
looks like a three-car garage it is a
2car garage with epoxy
flooring the third car garage was
converted converted into the
Mother-in-law Suite there is one of the
of the HVAC units in
here the garage door does open so this
area in general is very known for golf
carts so his thinking was that could
open up you could store a golf cart or
you could convert this and make that
into a living space then you have your
full kitchen with all of your
appliances again fridge
stove microwave and dishwasher all come
with the mother-in-law sweek sweet full
bedroom and full bathroom with a shower
and we have three entrances to the
backyard in the back patio which I
thought was very well thought out from
the Mother-in-law Suite from the dining
space and from the master bedroom this
backyard is awesome uh the house
actually sits on four acres you have
mature pecan and oak trees all over the
property there was a lot done to this
backyard the pool was completely re done
by a local pool company here all new
equipment all new lining a lot of work
went into that and you can tell it's
great uh there is in that house right
there there's actually a well so it's a
40t Well the Water Supplies all of the
irrigation and there is City water to
the property but a homeowner could
convert that convert the home to well
water if they wanted to uh there's a
basketball and pickle ball court pickle
ball I guess it's getting really popular
all new Landscaping currently no rear
Neighbors which is
nice and in the back there there is a
big storage building that was converted
it is currently being used as a gym but
you really could do whatever you want
with
that welcome to your gym so the floors
were just refinished and like I
mentioned there is a heat pump in here
so you won't stay too hot and stuffy as
you're working out you could really do
whatever you wanted with the space
though one of the best things I think
about this property is actually the
location we are on 4 acres and it's very
private but you're only 3 minutes away
from I35 so your location is fantastic
to get to things you're about 40 minutes
from Austin Texas you're 40 minutes from
Waco and 10 minutes from grocery stores
and amenities so if you're looking for
some peace and quiet but want to be
close to everything this would be your
home I hope you enjoyed enjoyed today's
home tour if you'd like any more
information on this property or any
others in the area you can find my
contact information below don't forget
to subscribe and click the Bell so that
you can stay up to date on all the
latest market trends happenings and cool
things going on here in Central Texas
until next time I'm Andrea dudic guiding
your next move with Insight care and
clear communication